<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ReFarmer.net</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ReFarmer.net</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Soil Sensing Mission continues</title>
      <link>/post/soil-sensing-mission-continues/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/soil-sensing-mission-continues/</guid>
      <description>In the wake of Project GROW -whose EU funding ran out last autumn- there remains some &amp;ldquo;afterbirth&amp;rdquo; in the form of (a) soil sensors in the ground, in the care of (b) ReFarmers determined to continue monitoring the conditions of our soils ongoingly, with or without any outside support.
So it is that i have this historical record of Surface Soil Temperature and Light (Top Left and Right, respectively, in these graphs), and Surface Soil Moisture and %change (Bottom Left and Right) for 15 representative sites around my farm, for the period from mid-August 2018 to present (mid-Feb 2020).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Simple Polytunnel to SMART Greenhouse</title>
      <link>/post/from-simple-polytunnel-to-smart-greenhouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/from-simple-polytunnel-to-smart-greenhouse/</guid>
      <description>By getting plants off to the best possible start, you can avoid all sorts of problems that would otherwise crop up later. This is the fundamental truth on which our SMART Greenhouse project is based; it is also the filter through which we look at our Simple Polytunnel as it stands, and consider how we can improve conditions to produce the most robust, disease-resistant and nutrient-dense plants, as efficiently as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SLOfood Lagos: Gaining Momentum</title>
      <link>/post/slofood-lagos-gaining-momentum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/slofood-lagos-gaining-momentum/</guid>
      <description>Though the concept of &amp;ldquo;Slow Food&amp;rdquo; was a thing some time ago -today, maybe not so much- the SLO (Seasonal/ Local/ Organic) food movement here in Lagos is really gaining traction, as locals are coming to understand what it means and appreciate the many benefits.
As we are challenged by the growing number of discriminating consumers to explain exactly what this means to us at Quinta Vale da Lama, and what we are doing about it, we are elevating core principles to the level of policy:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter ReFarming</title>
      <link>/post/winter-refarming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/winter-refarming/</guid>
      <description>Beautiful time of year here, in this landscape so liberally sprinkled with almond flowers -introduced as a form of artificial snow, according to legend. Beautiful, but also challenging, in that Good Stewardship of these trees and the soil in which they grown involves a lot of work that needs doing in this short winter season, when days are short and weather unpredictable.
SO: There&amp;rsquo;s a lot going on! And not much time for squinting and pecking at the computer screen&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic HTML Elements</title>
      <link>/post/basic-elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/basic-elements/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The main purpose of this article is to make sure that all basic HTML Elements are decorated with CSS so as to not miss any possible elements when creating new themes for Hugo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>/post/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>/post/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo uses the excellent &lt;a href=&#34;https://golang.org/&#34;&gt;Go&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://golang.org/pkg/html/template/&#34;&gt;html/template&lt;/a&gt; library for
its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very
small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of
logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other
template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of
similarities in Go templates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Go to Hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the Hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>