<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ReFarmer.net</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ReFarmer.net</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fork</title>
      <link>/post/the-fork/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-fork/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;When you come to a fork in the road, take it!&amp;rdquo; quoth the late great Yogi Berra, who rates second to none in the ranks of our great American folk heroes, as much for these gnomic words of wisdom as for his immortal achievements on the baseball diamond. Let the post-modern deconstructivists make of this what they will; any ReFarmer worth his salt holds this wisdom close at heart, without having to think too much about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soil Sensing Mission continues</title>
      <link>/post/soil-sensing-mission-continues/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/soil-sensing-mission-continues/</guid>
      <description>In the wake of Project GROW -whose EU funding ran out last autumn- there remains some &amp;ldquo;afterbirth&amp;rdquo; in the form of (a) soil sensors in the ground, in the care of (b) ReFarmers determined to continue monitoring the conditions of our soils ongoingly, with or without any outside support.
So it is that i have this historical record of Surface Soil Temperature and Light (Top Left and Right, respectively, in these graphs), and Surface Soil Moisture and %change (Bottom Left and Right) for 15 representative sites around my farm, for the period from mid-August 2018 to present (mid-Feb 2020).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Simple Polytunnel to SMART Greenhouse</title>
      <link>/post/from-simple-polytunnel-to-smart-greenhouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/from-simple-polytunnel-to-smart-greenhouse/</guid>
      <description>By getting plants off to the best possible start, you can avoid all sorts of problems that would otherwise crop up later. This is the fundamental truth on which our SMART Greenhouse project is based; it is also the filter through which we look at our Simple Polytunnel as it stands, and consider how we can improve conditions to produce the most robust, disease-resistant and nutrient-dense plants, as efficiently as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SLOfood Lagos: Gaining Momentum</title>
      <link>/post/slofood-lagos-gaining-momentum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/slofood-lagos-gaining-momentum/</guid>
      <description>Though the concept of &amp;ldquo;Slow Food&amp;rdquo; was a thing some time ago -today, maybe not so much- the SLO (Seasonal/ Local/ Organic) food movement here in Lagos is really gaining traction, as locals are coming to understand what it means and appreciate the many benefits.
As we are challenged by the growing number of discriminating consumers to explain exactly what this means to us at Quinta Vale da Lama, and what we are doing about it, we are elevating core principles to the level of policy:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter ReFarming</title>
      <link>/post/winter-refarming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/winter-refarming/</guid>
      <description>Beautiful time of year here, in this landscape so liberally sprinkled with almond flowers -introduced as a form of artificial snow, according to legend. Beautiful, but also challenging, in that Good Stewardship of these trees and the soil in which they grown involves a lot of work that needs doing in this short winter season, when days are short and weather unpredictable.
SO: There&amp;rsquo;s a lot going on! And not much time for squinting and pecking at the computer screen&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>